SILSILA HAMDARD

JUNIOR UI/UX/GRAPHIC DESIGNER

CONTACT

- A Harrow, London
- **C** 07502005836
- ☐ https://silsila.co.uk/

SKILLS

Software

Adobe InDesign Adobe XD Adobe Illustrator Photoshop Procreate (iPad)



PROFILE

My portfolio is available at silsila.co.uk

As a UI/UX and Graphic designer, I approach projects from a fresh perspective. By producing these projects I am learning how to approach problems effectively and plan accordingly.

All of the following require creativity, patience and thinking which are skills I both possess and am actively growing. Whether it is working on a new project or designing something very complex, I strive to impress and to ensure my services are valuable.

I am currently working for a company called kindcody as a freelancer. I worked as a junior react developer and after 5 months of development, I changed to a UI/UX/Graphic designer. I am now responsible for UI/UX and branding of this company.

As for now, I would love to join a company that I could work with since I am working remotely as a freelancer all the time. It would be nice to be in an office along with a team I could strive to grow and learn with. I also want to improve my design skills in a creative environment.

EXPERIENCE

Mar 2019 -Present

kindcody

UI/UX Designer, London

- User interface (UI) Web/App
- User experience (UX) Web/App
- Branding (Logo, font, colour and etc)
- Competitor Research
- Product enhancement and development

Nov 2018 -Mar 2019

kindcody

Junior React Developer, London

- Use React, NextJS, ExpressJS, ES6, Firebase, Heroku, in my tech stack
- State management done via basic Context routed from the top-level component
- Project management via JIRA and delivered in Scrum Sprints.
- Weekly meetings with updates on the progress

Jun 2016 -Sep 2016

Weavee

Junior software developer, London

Assist

the developers with styling modules in their MVC tech stack.

- Use HTML5/SCSS to build an interactive CV with data coming from Rails
- Create and follow up on potential sales leads, organise and attend meetings purposed to generate innovative ideas for the start-up.

EDUCATION

2018

Bachelors Degree of Computer Science

University of West London, London

- Course Highlights: Java development, Database design, Project Management, Web design, Computer Architecture, Mathematics and Logic, Computing Algorithms
- Completed and passed the first year

BTEC Level 3 Extended Diploma in IT/Software Development

Stanmore College, London

- D*D*D* all modules completed to the highest grade.
- Course Highlights: Java development,
 Database design, Project management, Web design, Computer architecture